# Anna Rusyayeva

Email: annarsve@gmail.com Mobile: +7(922)159-60-30

Github: https://github.com/VanillaWulf

Linkedin: https://www.linkedin.com/in/anna-rusyaeva-6b1276148

#### **SUMMARY**

Five years of experience in commercial development for varying business areas provided me with the skill to understand client's goals and to create tasks to achieve it. Thanks to a solid set of marketing tools, I promote the relevant customers in the right direction according to the needed intention. Moreover, with the help of excellent building communications with current teams and contractors, I clearly plan tasks and hand over projects on time.

#### **SKILLS**

- **Agile** (SCRUM, Kanban, scrumban)
- Managing projects (Trello, Jira)
- E-commerce (Yandex Direct, Yandex Metrics, Google AdWords, Google Analytics)
- Market research
- Marketing (POSM, presentations, mailings)
- Sales analytics
- User demand analysis
- Developing cases for new products/features (IDEF, UML)
- **Design** (sketch, moqups, figma, adobe products)
- Strong technical stack (HTML, CSS, JS, ReactJS, Angular, git)

#### **WORK EXPERIENCE**

### Front-End Developer - Bank 'Tochka'

- User demand analysis
- Marking-up with material design
- · Creating tasks in Trello and Jira
- Making user scenario using moqups
- Creating new components on Angular 2
- Improving usability
- Participate and organization of meetings
- Support written parts

### Senior Marketing Manager - 000 'Ideco'

*October 2017 – June 2018* 

July 2018 – present time

- Launch, maintaining and updating websites
- Writing technical specifications for designers and programmers
- Monitoring tasks using Jira and Trello
- Planning budgets
- Creating roadmaps
- SMM
- Activities for attraction leads (mailings, contests, articles in popular magazines, publications in top security channels)
- Typesetting e-mail pages
- Working with mailing lists databases (collect and parsing)
- Creating POS materials



**PROJECTS** 

#### **Test your security**



Marketing landing page for creating customer interest through potential threats

#### **Control the traffic**



Product landing page, attracting over 1000 people per month.

# Catalog of projects



Catalog of multi-panel house structures

#### **Catalog of houses**



Redesign catalog structure for increasing the organic traffic by • Sales analytics 40%

- Making bases for cold calling
- Quarterly reports about efficiency of marketing activities

## **SEO Specialist** - Advertising Agency 'Index Art'

January 2017 - October 2017

- Technical auditing (layout, structure, accessibility)
- Designing and correcting a site structure
- Writing technical specifications for revising and updating
- Over 150 closing tasks monitoring
- Creating semantics cores
- Designing and implementation metadata
- Content updating, rendering a page layout
- Creating monthly reports for customers

# Context Advertising and SEO Specialist -

December 2015 - September 2016

Advertising Agency 'ManyLetters'

- Creating and running campaigns in Yandex.Direct, Google AdWords, MyTarget
- Coordination updates with clients
- Writing specifications for programmers
- Creating monthly reports for customers

## **Software Engineer -**

October 2013 - September 2014

Special design bureau 'Peleng'

- Writing technical specification for software
- Studying functionality of software and detecting its flaws
- Revising software in C++
- Modular and integration testing



Newsletter for the company.

#### **EDUCATION**

Beijing University of Aeronautics and Astronautics *Master of Computer Science* 

February 2015

Courses and Certificates: Build Front-End Web Apps from Scratch course

Professional HTML & CSS, level 1

**Ural Federal University** 

Systems Administration

**Ural Federal University** 

**Ural Federal University** 

Master of Computer Science in Technology in Mathematical Software and Information

Higher Professional Education in Legal Regulation of Business

2013

2013

2015

Bachelor of Computer Science in Technology in Design and Technology of Electronic Means

#### **LANGUAGES**

Russian – native speaker English – B2

**Domain relocation** 



Domain relocation without organic traffic loses

# **Mailing**



# **Products mailing**

# CERTIFICATIONS